A Guide to the John Leonard Fulmer Agricultural Studies Collection
University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library, #4554
John Leonard Fulmer Agricultural Studies Collection 1930-1949, n.d.
University of Virginia. Library. Special Collections Dept. Alderman Library University of Virginia Charlottesville, Virginia 22903 USA
4554
ca. 35 items
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Gift, 25 Nov 1953
Container List
- Commodity Economics 202; Market-Sharing, 1940 (Box Box 1)
- Marketing 142; Marketing of Fruits and Vegetables, 1932-1934; (2 folders) (Box Box 1)
- Farm Management Lectures, 1935 (Box Box 1)
- Seminar Addresses, 1933-1934; (2 folders) (Box Box 1)
- Marketing, no date (Box Box 1)
- Rural Economy 151, 1933-1934 (Box Box 2)
- Agricultural Economics 208; Research Methods and Land Appraisal, 1932-1934 (Box Box 2)
- Land Appraisal, 1933-1934 (Box Box 2)
- Farm Management 115; Prices, 1933-1934 (Box Box 2)
- Farm Management; Prices, 1933-1934 (Box Box 2)
- Marketing 143, 1934 (Box Box 2)
- Farm Management 102, 1933-1934 (Box Box 2)
- Economics of Enterprise, 1930-1934 (Box Box 2)
- Farm Management 15; Prices, 1932-1934 (Box Box 2)
- Agricultural Progress in Cotton Belt since 1920, 1947 (Box Box 3)
- Albemarle County Survey -- Crop Year 1947 (Box Box 3)
- A Comparative Analysis of the Receipts and Expenses of a Tractor and Mule Farm of Equal Size, 1937 (Box Box 3)
- The Cost of Mule Power in Cotton Production, 1945 Dec (Box Box 3)
- Cotton Markets and Marketing; Preliminary Report to Pace Committee -- National Cotton Council on Project II, no date (Box Box 3)
- Cotton Yield Variability Study Book I, Folder I: Methodology Analysis, no date (Box Box 4)
- Cotton Yield Variability Study Book I, Folder II: Methodology Analysis, no date (Box Box 4)
- Cotton Yield Variability Study Book II, Folder I: Miscellaneous Information, Long Hand Tabulation, no date (Box Box 4)
- Cotton Yield Variability Study Book II, Folder II: Miscellaneous Information, Longhand Tabulation, no date (Box Box 4)
- Cotton Yield Variability Study (Upper Piedmont) Book III, Folder I: Miscellaneous Information, Longhand Tabulation, no date (Box Box 5)
- Cotton Yield Variability Study (Upper Piedmont) Book III, Folder II: Miscellaneous Information, Longhand Tabulation, no date (Box Box 5)
- Cotton Yield Variability Study (Upper Piedmont) Book III (Part II), Folder III: Miscellaneous Information, Longhand Tabulation, no date (Box Box 5)
- Cotton Yield Summary Book III (Part II), Folder IV, no date (Box Box 5)
- Cotton Yield Summary Book IV, Folder I, no date (Box Box 5)
- Cotton Yield Summary Book VII, Folder I, no date (Box Box 6)
- Cotton Yield Summary Book VII, Folder II, no date (Box Box 6)
- Cotton Yield Summary Book VII (Part II), Folder III, no date (Box Box 6)
- Cotton Yield Summary Book VIII, Folder I, no date (Box Box 6)
- Cotton Yield Summary Book VIII, Folder II, no date (Box Box 6)
- Cotton Yield Summary Book VIII, Folder III, no date (Box Box 7)
- Cotton Yield Summary Book IX, Folder I, no date (Box Box 7)
- Cotton Yield Summary Book IX, Folder II, no date (Box Box 7)
- Cotton Yield Summary Book X, Folder I, no date (Box Box 7)
- Cotton Yield Summary Book X, Folder II, no date (Box Box 7)
- Cotton Yield Summary Book XI, Folder I, no date (Box Box 8)
- Cotton Yield Summary Book XI (Part II), Folder I, no date (Box Box 8)
- Cotton Yield Summary Book XI (Part II), Folder II, no date (Box Box 8)
- Cotton Yield Summary Book XII, Folder I, no date (Box Box 8)
- Cotton Yield Summary Book XII, Folder II, no date (Box Box 8)
- Cotton Yield Summary Book XIII, Folder I, no date (Box Box 9)
- Cotton Yield Summary Book XIII, Folder II, no date (Box Box 9)
- Cotton Yield Summary Book XIII, Folder III, no date (Box Box 9)
- Cotton Yield Summary Book XIV, Folder I, no date (Box Box 9)
- Cotton Yield Summary Book XIV, Folder II, no date (Box Box 9)
- Cotton Yield Summary Book XIV, Folder III, no date (Box Box 9)
- Cotton Yield Summary Book XIV (Part II), Folder IV, no date (Box Box 10)
- Cotton Yield Summary Book XIV (Part II), Folder V, no date (Box Box 10)
- Cotton Yield Summary Book XIV (Part II), Folder VI, no date (Box Box 10)